(upbeat music)
♪ Welcome to your life ♪
♪ There's no turning back ♪
♪ Even while we sleep ♪
♪ We will find you ♪
♪ Acting on your best behavior ♪
♪ Turn your back on Mother Nature ♪
♪ Everybody wants to rule the world ♪
♪ It's my own design ♪
♪ It's my own remorse ♪
♪ Help me to decide ♪
♪ Help me make the ♪
♪ Most of freedom and of pleasure ♪
♪ Nothing ever lasts forever ♪
♪ Everybody wants to rule the world ♪
♪ There's a room where
the light won't find you ♪
♪ Holding hands while the
walls come tumbling down ♪
♪ When they do, I'll be right behind you ♪
♪ So glad we've almost made it ♪
♪ So sad they had to fade it ♪
♪ Everybody wants to rule the world ♪
(bright music)
♪ I can't stand this indecision ♪
♪ Married with a lack of vision ♪
♪ Everybody wants to rule the ♪
♪ Say that you'll never,
never, never, never need it ♪
♪ One headline, why believe it ♪
♪ Everybody wants to rule the world ♪
(bright music)
♪ All for freedom and for pleasure ♪
♪ Nothing ever lasts forever ♪
♪ Everybody wants to rule the world ♪
(bright music)